<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Data Decoded</title>
    <link>https://shauntothemoon.github.io/portfolio/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Data Decoded</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 06 Jun 2023 16:32:15 +0200</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://shauntothemoon.github.io/portfolio/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Should your funnel dashboards look like a funnel</title>
      <link>https://shauntothemoon.github.io/portfolio/projects/should_your_funnel_dashboards_look_like_a_funnel/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Jun 2023 16:32:15 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://shauntothemoon.github.io/portfolio/projects/should_your_funnel_dashboards_look_like_a_funnel/</guid>
      <description>By introducing this project, I would like to discuss an interesting and simple question I encountered while working on funnel optimization:
Should the funnel dashboards really look like a funnel?
This project is in fact a relatively tiny dashboard I built and redesigned for the funnel optimizations of a product from our organization. Though it may look tiny, it has been used for the stakeholder&amp;rsquo;s regular reporting as a sole source of truth for funnel traffics - which means it will be used as a data visualization in slides, many, many, many times.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Case Study Inequalities in the Predictive Policing of LAPD</title>
      <link>https://shauntothemoon.github.io/portfolio/blog/case-_study_inequalities_in_the_predictive_policing_of_lapd/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Jun 2023 15:00:05 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://shauntothemoon.github.io/portfolio/blog/case-_study_inequalities_in_the_predictive_policing_of_lapd/</guid>
      <description>Before you read&amp;hellip; This is in fact a case study that I conducted during my master program, which puts a huge emphasis on reflecting how extensively used data could cause more - instead of less - systematical violence. It received 9, a very high mark in the Dutch higher education system, and is currently used by my professor as an example for future students.
Though I am now working towards a career in data analysis and strategies, the academic trainings I received always help me be mindful of consequences of what I (or we) could cause with data.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
